Are we okay?
What do you mean?
There's something you're not telling me.
[SCOFFS] I'll admit it.
Dude, I…
I'm in love with you.
Jordan, say something.
Huh?
Is there any way we can lower the cost
of the additional security measures
you proposed?
That's all?
[CHUCKLES]
I thought…
Thought what?
Nothing.
Um, okay. I'll review it again.
Good night.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ralph.
I-I just want to…
I just need to talk to you about Charm.
So,
are you here because you're
finally breaking up with her?
No.
She's the one breaking up with me.
She's willing to let me go
just so I can make up with you.
I'm sorry, son.
[BILLY] Ralph.
You may want to add something?
Because if you've set your mind
on something,
you don't wait for the perfect time.
You choose the moment.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Okay. Um…
What I'm trying to say is
that even if…
a lot of people are against us,
Charm…
will you marry me?
Didn't I tell you
to fix your relationship
with your mom first?
Babe, that's more important.
I'll be the happiest
if you will say yes, dear.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
My son said that
you're willing to let him go
just so that he can fix our relationship.
And Billy,
you never stopped telling my son
to always reach out to me.
Thank you.
Charm, I'm so sorry.
Ralph, what are you waiting for?
Ask her again.
- Uh, Charm.
- Mm?
Babe?
Will you marry me?
- Yes!
- [RALPH CHUCKLES]
- Of course, yes!
- [STAFF CHEER]
Oh my God!
[ROWENA] Wow.
[LUCY] How's the search
for your other family?
[ENRICO]
I go to her grave once in a while,
hoping that her mom
and sister would visit,
but…
[LUCY] And you found Billy's family first.
Does Billy know that
she has siblings other than Oliver?
I don't know how to tell her.
If I were you, I'd tell her everything.
Sure, she's going to get hurt,
but that's better than
lying to her forever.
- [ENRICO] Where--
- There's a fight!
- Auntie…
- [ENRICO] Wait up!
- Hurry up!
- Calm down.
Hurry!
Why--
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENRICO EXHALES]
- Ta-da!
- [BILLY CLEARS THROAT]
Did you think we forgot?
[OLIVER CLAPPING]
Happy birthday.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Happy birthday, Dad.
[OLIVER] Make a wish! Make a wish!
[OLIVER] Boom!
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
I'll take you
to Billy's favorite restaurant.
They serve seafood there.
Do you like seafood?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Okay. Let's go, Auntie Pres?
- [PRECIOUS] Mm.
- Okay, let's bring this.
- Let's box it up.
Happy birthday, Pa.
I'll check your wound, Ma.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tsk.
We need to have the doctor
check on it again.
I want to leave.
I can't take it anymore.
Ma…
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLATES, CUTLERY CLINKING]
Pa.
What did you wish for earlier?
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm Private Investigator Jimenez.
Uh…
Have you found my wife and daughters?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Your eldest daughter, Abigail?
[JIMENEZ] She died in a fire.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
FIRE BURNS DOWN HOME
[ENRICO] Abi, dear…
I'm sorry.
I wasn't a good father to you and Bea.
I promise…
I will find your mother and sister.
I don't know if Billy will ever
be able to forgive me
for what I'm about to tell her.
I know this is too much.
But she needs to know the truth.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I wished that…
That…
[PRECIOUS] Enrico?
Are you okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I wished that we'd always be like this.
Happy
and all together.
[OLIVER] Of course, Papa.
We won't be apart anymore.
Right, Billy?
Yes, that's right.
We're finally complete.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUSY TONE]
- [BUSY TONE]
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Enrico?
- Oh.
Uh…
Why are you still up?
I'm just finishing up doing
the canteen's inventory.
Hmm.
Enrico, are you really okay?
Billy and I noticed earlier
that you seemed to have something
weighing on your mind.
Is something bothering you?
Auntie Pres…
Oh. Sorry, sorry.
I'll go now. Go to bed too.
Okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY'S LAWYER] The other
party is relentless.
They don't want to say why
they're mad at you.
I can't think of any reason, Attorney.
There are cases of
targeted harassment, Billy.
Sometimes,
they don't have any clear motive.
It's just because of obsession.
Attorney, I just want you to reassure me
that Bea can't do anything else
to help herself and her mother.
We're doing everything that we can.
But we cannot stop the process.
Mariela still needs to undergo
psychiatric evaluation.
And if proven that
she's mentally unfit, then…
So what are you saying, Attorney?
So Bea still has a chance of
getting what she wants?
But the evaluation may take weeks.
Even months.
- [CLICKS]
- [THUDS]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Mariela Mercado.
Miss, my mother doesn't need painkillers.
We cleaned her wound earlier, didn't we?
Yes, but I requested that, if possible,
she be transferred to a hospital.
We're already monitoring her condition.
That's not enough!
Is my request that hard?!
My mother needs--
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I'll take that.
[BEA] Thank you.
So annoying.
Here, Ma.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get some rest, Ma. Lie down first.
Go on.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BEA SIGHS DEEPLY]
[JAIL CELL RATTLING]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Tsk!
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Is Papa not coming home?
Isn't he joining us?
You're so dumb, aren't you?
You're stupid!
You really take after your father.
You're both useless!
Ma! Ma!
- Take her.
- Ma.
- Help her.
- Help! Ma.
Ma, wake up! Ma!
[CRYING] Ma!
[LABORED BREATHING]
- Abigail!
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Abigail! Abigail!
- [ABIGAIL BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Abigail.
The question is,
which one of us is the bigger thief?
A thief?
What the hell are you talking about?
If only you knew.
Knew what?
Why don't you just tell the truth,
so I can understand
where your anger is coming from?
What's your reason for going after me?
Ma.
No matter what happens,
don't tell them
that you know
they're Papa's second family.
Why not?
That's the truth.
Ma.
Please listen to me.
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[BEA] I was wrong, Ma.
The truth won't hurt us.
It may even save us both.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Attorney said Mariela
might get out of jail.
I can't let that happen, Auntie.
Of course.
Bea would do anything for her mother.
Just like you would for your father.
But that won't fix what happened.
Someone who is afraid to lose a loved one
is a tough opponent.
But fortunately, we are all safe.
And so is your father.
Like I told Jordan,
what happened to us was devastating.
But when I found out
that Dad didn't forget about me,
everything we had lost
didn't seem to matter anymore.
Because Dad came back to us.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
AMIHAN HOME
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
Is there a problem, Jordan?
- Grandpa?
- Did you get into a fight?
No, Grandpa.
There's just so much going on with Billy.
Her house burned down.
And LoveList is having problems
with investors.
But it's good that she and her father
have made amends.
You and your father are okay now?
Has he gotten his act together?
No, I'm talking about
Billy and her father.
- Not…
- [JUDE] Huh?
Never mind.
[HUFFS]
She's such a fighter, Grandpa.
Despite everything,
she's always there
for the people who need her.
[MOVING MUSIC PLAYING]
Even if it isn't easy…
Even though I know that
it could ruin our friendship…
I can't help it.
I'm falling in love with her.
["THE PUZZLE" BY
BELLE MARIANO PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Thank you for listening.
["THE PUZZLE" CONTINUES]
[JAIL CELL CREAKS OPEN]
- [INMATE 1] Sir, good evening.
- [JAIL GUARD] Go to sleep.
- [INMATE 2] Good night, sir.
- [JAIL GUARD] Okay.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Enough chitchat. Go to sleep!
- [BATON TAPS JAIL CELL]
- [DINO] We will be blessed
if we just trust His word and
dedicate our lives to Him.
- [JAIL CELL CLANGS]
- After you pray, go to sleep.
Yes, sir.
- [JAIL GUARD] Hit the sack!
- [INMATE 3] Yes, sir.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Is everything ready for Family Day?
Boss.
We can no longer use
the garbage holding area.
We checked last night.
The railings were replaced.
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[MUSIC FADES]
Attorney.
I can request to speak to Billy, right?
I can just relay your message to her.
No.
I have to tell her myself.
We need to talk in person.
Well, we can make a request.
But there's no guarantee
that she'll agree.
And besides, I'm your lawyer.
Anything you intend to say to her
should go through me first.
I know that.
But this is a personal matter.
So I want to talk to her alone
and tell her myself.
Whatever it is,
it's better if I know.
Because it might aggravate your case
even if you have good intentions.
What is it that you want
to say to Ms. Cariño?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Attorney.
Please submit a request
so I can personally talk to Billy.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We need to find
potential investors!
If not Claire, who?
If not the US,
then where?!
[ENRICO]
I just don't know how to say it
because I don't want to
hurt you again.
What is it?
Strong coffee
for a strong woman.
I don't think this is enough.
We're going to stay up
all night at work.
I disappointed our chief again.
Hey, don't take it to heart.
It's just work.
Mm-hmm.
You're one to talk. I saw how negative
your vibe became earlier.
Bea asked to speak
with you in person.
Can't she just say whatever it is
through her lawyer?
[Granado] Bea's adamant.
She insists it's a… family matter?
I don't have all day.
I'm a busy person.
Billy, sorry.
Have you run out of tricks
to escape from this?
Your apology won't erase
all the harm you've done to my family.
I wronged you.
I wronged your family too.
- I did it because you stole from me.
- I never stole anything from you.